{
    "qna": {
        "result1": {
            "question": "A person with well-developed abdominal muscles is said to have a what?",
            "answer1": "One-pack",
            "answer2": "Six-pack",
            "answer3": "12-pack",
            "answer4": "Family-pack",
            "correct": 2
            
        },
        "result2": {
            "question": "Which two words traditionally appear onscreen at the termination of a feature film?",
            "answer1": "The End",
            "answer2": "The Conclusion",
            "answer3": "The Finish",
            "answer4": "The Pizza Rolss are done",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result3": {
            "question": "A magnet would most likely attract which of the following?",
            "answer1": "Metal",
            "answer2": "Plastic",
            "answer3": "Wood",
            "answer4": "The wrong man",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result4": {
            "question": "Which of these names is not in the title of a Shakespeare play?",
            "answer1": "Hamlet",
            "answer2": "Romeo",
            "answer3": "Macbeth",
            "answer4": "Darren",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result5": {
            "question": "Where did Scotch whisky originate?",
            "answer1": "Ireland",
            "answer2": "Wales",
            "answer3": "The United States",
            "answer4": "Scotland",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result6": {
            "question": "What name is traditionally given to the party held for a woman who is expecting a baby?",
            "answer1": "Baby drizzle",
            "answer2": "Baby shower",
            "answer3": "Baby downpour",
            "answer4": "Baby deluge",
            "correct": 2
            
        },
        "result7": {
            "question": "In fancy hotels, it is traditional for what tantalizing treat to be left on your pillow?",
            "answer1": "A pretzel",
            "answer2": "An apple",
            "answer3": "A mint",
            "answer4": "a photo of wolf Blitzer",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result8": {
            "question": "In the United States, what is traditionally the proper way to address a judge?",
            "answer1": "Your holiness",
            "answer2": "Your honor",
            "answer3": "Your eminence",
            "answer4": "You da man!",
            "correct": 2
            
        },
        "result9": {
            "question": "Which of these pairs of apps offers roughly the same type of service?",
            "answer1": "Snapchat and Grubhub",
            "answer2": "Whatsapp and SHAREit",
            "answer3": "TikTok and Spotify",
            "answer4": "Lyft and Uber",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result10": {
            "question": "The popular children's song: It's Raining, It's Pouring mentions an old man doing what?",
            "answer1": "Snoring",
            "answer2": "Cooking",
            "answer3": "Laughing",
            "answer4": "Yelling at squirrels",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result11": {
            "question": "At a restaurant, someone who: foots the bill does what?",
            "answer1": "Kisses it",
            "answer2": "Kisses it",
            "answer3": "Hopes to get lucky",
            "answer4": "Pays it",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result12": {
            "question": "In which of these films does Whoopi Goldberg dress up as a nun?",
            "answer1": "Sister Act",
            "answer2": "Ghost",
            "answer3": "The Color Purple",
            "answer4": "How Judas Got His Groove Back",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result13": {
            "question": "If someone asked to see your ID, what might you show them?",
            "answer1": "Your tongue",
            "answer2": "Your teeth",
            "answer3": "Your passport",
            "answer4": "The door",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result14": {
            "question": "According to a common phrase, a person who takes chances is: going out on a what?",
            "answer1": "Limb",
            "answer2": "Horse",
            "answer3": "Skateboard",
            "answer4": "Nude beach",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result15": {
            "question": "Due to the geographical areas they represented, the opposing sides of the US Civil War were known by what names?",
            "answer1": "The Hills and the Valleys",
            "answer2": "The Cities and the Farms",
            "answer3": "The North and the South ",
            "answer4": "The Kool and the Gang",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result16": {
            "question": "According to the old saying,: love of what: is the root of all evil?",
            "answer1": "Food",
            "answer2": "Money",
            "answer3": "Clothing",
            "answer4": "Reality television",
            "correct": 2
            
        },
        "result17": {
            "question": "A geologist would likely be LEAST helpful for answering questions about which of the following?",
            "answer1": "Granite boulders",
            "answer2": "Precious stones",
            "answer3": "Igneous rocks",
            "answer4": "Fruity Pebbles",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result18": {
            "question": "A feisty train is the hero of a classic children's book titled The Little Engine That what?",
            "answer1": "Ran",
            "answer2": "Cried",
            "answer3": "Could",
            "answer4": "Opened a can of whupass",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result19": {
            "question": "A person who is not a banker and lends money at an extremely high interest rate is known as what?",
            "answer1": "Loan shark",
            "answer2": "Green snake",
            "answer3": "Paper tiger",
            "answer4": "Brother-in-law",
            "correct": 1
            
        },
        "result20": {
            "question": "A well-known lyric in the holiday song: Silver Bells promises that soon it will be what?",
            "answer1": "July 4th weekend",
            "answer2": "Halloween night",
            "answer3": "Christmas Day",
            "answer4": "National Burrito Month",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result21": {
            "question": "When a person is rudely ignored, he is said to be getting what?",
            "answer1": "Hot knee",
            "answer2": "Warm toe",
            "answer3": "Could shoulder",
            "answer4": "Hix car fixed",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result22": {
            "question": "A common piece of advice goes,: Be there or be what?",
            "answer1": "Bare",
            "answer2": "Square",
            "answer3": "Awara",
            "answer4": "All alone as usual",
            "correct": 2
            
        },
        "result23": {
            "question": "And many more is a line commonly sung at the end of what traditional ditty?",
            "answer1": "Old MacDonald",
            "answer2": "Jolly Good Fellow",
            "answer3": "Happy Birthday",
            "answer4": "Home on the Range",
            "correct": 3
            
        },
        "result24": {
            "question": "If you're trying to find other players in a game of hide-and-seek, what are you most likely called?",
            "answer1": "Butterbean",
            "answer2": "Stinky",
            "answer3": "Dunce",
            "answer4": "IT",
            "correct": 4
            
        },
        "result25": {
            "question": "Which of these phrases is slang for: someone who has a strong and unyielding attitude?",
            "answer1": "Boiled ham",
            "answer2": "Tough cookie",
            "answer3": "Ruffled chip",
            "answer4": "Soggy cereal",
            "correct": 2
            
        }
        
        
    }
}